Great Grandpa, what are you watching?
I'm studying the foundations of our Bitchun Society.
People dressed so funny then.  Why would
anyone wear such a funny thing on their head?
Ha, believe it or not, people used to have
to go outside.  That's called a hat.
Outside? A hat?
Yes, outside on the earth's surface, not inside these
bitchun buildings, in the daylight...
A hat is a helmet to protect you from the cold...
I'm finishing writing my history of the 21st century right now.
Do you know how I learned so much about
how our Bitchun Society was formed?
No.
Well, little one, let me tell you.
The founders of our Bitchun Society kept immaculate
records in The Internet Archive.
What's The Internet Archive?
Everything's recorded now, was it different then?
Very different...
Corporations...
Corporations owned the voices of the people
before the Founders found The Archive.
Many voices have been lost.
What do you mean, many voices were lost, great grandfather?
If someone didn't license their work
using Creative Commons licenses,
and upload it to The Internet Archive,
it wasn't free for individuals to share,
it belonged to a corporation.
Those who used The Archive and Creative Commons
were free to share ideas without corporate control.
Share! Remix! Upload!
Those voices we can still hear today.
And forever, right?
Have your voice heard forever:
use The Internet Archive
and Creative Commons licenses.
http://archive.org/
http://creativecommons.org/
for more information
CCopyleft Papyromancer
January, 2009